Mr Su
I've been watching Su's Escort Agency all morning.
Su Yuejiao never went out.
Humph.
She was taught a lesson by me.
She was scared.
Keep watching.
Once she goes out,
go and stop her at once.
Oh, by the way,
Escort leader
There's another thing.
Gong Xi, Gong Xi
Our boss didn't do morning exercises today,
nor did he escort anyone.
He seems to have stayed in the ancestral hall all night.
Do you think it's because of the marriage selection,
or the uncle?
Isn't it the same thing?
At this time,
don't take any escort mission.
If there is such a escort,
we can pretend to be sick
like the Old Master.
Ah, right.
Then we'll beat you until you get better.
Boss, are you okay?
I'm fine.
You've thought it through?
Ah.
What have you thought through?
I've thought through that
A woman still has to get married.
Right?
Our family still has to rely on me.
I've already found you a marriage.
Dad also agreed.
Where is he?
He'll be here in the afternoon.
This time I'm sure you can get married.
I really admire you sometimes.
You can talk nonsense at any time.
You said I couldn't get married yesterday.
and today you say I'll get married.
My master is going to get married.
Hey, young man, don't make trouble.
What does your master's marriage have to do with our escort agency?
We need to take
an escort for the bride.
Did your master teach you to speak like that?
No way.
You're such a jinx.
Ning'an County.
That's right.
I'll take this escort.
What?
Are you sure she's heading to Ning'an?
I heard it with my own ears.
Perfect.
There's only one road to Ning'an.
It's the perfect place to make a move.
You...
Hey.
Gather some men.
Go and rob Su Yuejiao's escort.
Remember,
if you can't kill her, cripple her.
Don't worry, escort leader.
I'll do it right away.
Rocks in the way.
Stay alert.
Okay.
Spring breeze turns into rain,
gentle as water.
Miss Shui,
the tune of "Between Water and Cloud"
is really amazing.
I feel uncomfortable
if I don't listen to it for a day.
You only praised Ms. Shui.
What about our newly composed dance?
Today
is the first time to dance.
This dance is like spring breeze melting into water,
very gentle.
If the dance steps are more decisive,
it must be more lively.
You're so discerning, Young Master Cheng.
After your trip to Yunjing City,
your taste has become more unique.
You must have met many beauties
that inspired you.
The women in Yunjing City
are indeed extraordinary.
Boss, as I said,
there's gonna be a fierce battle with the bandits.
We'd better save our energy.
Yeah, boss.
If we are late,
we won't finish the escort.
Help them.
Or check the other carts?
They were
bumpy just now.
That's my great invention.
The inspiration of the invention
is to control the speed of the cart.
Boss.
Please read it.
The shaft is a piece of wood.
It's broken in the middle.
If you want to turn, let the horse go first.
The carriage won't be bumpy.
Speak human language.
A piece of wood is divided into four parts.
It's useless.
You are really good.
Go to work.
Does he know
it's dangerous to change the escort team's things?
Miss Yan, there are rocks in the road.
We're cleaning up.
It won't delay your auspicious hour.
Thank you, Chief Escort Su.
As usual,
I'll deal with the leader.
You take care of the escort cart.
Boss,
shall we rob it?
There is something wrong with these stones.
They look like the work of the White Wolf.
Wait a minute.
Yes.
Help me.
Ah.
Facha.
I feel...
I feel that
the boss is a little angry today.
Ah.
Didn't you hear before we set off?
Uncle-in-law wants to arrange a blind date for My Lord.
Blind date?
Uncle-in-law? Shh.
Didn't Uncle-in-law always forbid My Lord to recruit a son-in-law?
There must be something wrong.
That's why My Lord rushed to take the escort.
To escape.
After all the trouble My Lord has been through,
She can't get married in Yunjing,
nor can she find a husband.
Well,
she can't find a bandit.
Who said she would find a bandit?
You keep talking about bandits,
making her nervous.
Look,
if she manages the family,
she must be urged to get married.
She's angry
How can she not be angry?
I think
she is expecting some bandits.
Ah?
Let her boss fight with them to vent her anger.
Shut up.
Su's Escort Agency in Yunjing City
is passing through your place today.
I'm Su Yuejiao.
I hope you can
do us a favor.
Leave the escort cart here.
Kowtow three times and I'll let you go.
Su's Escort Agency.
The escort lives with the escort.
What a load of nonsense.
You're really smart, boss.
Do we still need to do anything?
When White Wolf kills them,
we'll go down and pick up the leftovers.
At that time,
we can say that we were robbed by White Wolf.
We can get something for ourselves.
Stop!
What should we do now?
Su's Escort Agency, the escort lives with the escort.
You hold them back.
I'll take the escort cart and go first.
I'm sorry.
If we win, we'll let you go.
If we lose, leave the goods here.
Su's Escort Agency,
the escort...
That's enough.
Leave the escort cart here.
Everyone, let's talk.
I'm talking to you.
You, give me the escort cart.
Then we can get off work.
No way.
Our Su's Escort Agency
is with the escort.
Why are you so stubborn?
Go!
Young Master, you are so...
Are you thinking of a tender
confidante?
Well.
I'm thinking of a girl.
But she is not tender,
not at all.
She is more like
General's Order.
Young Master, is your beloved here?
Young Master, your bride is coming.
Master is urging you to go home and prepare.
Go away.
Don't you see the girls are rehearsing?
Wait until I finish listening to it.
The County Sheriff is here for the girls again.
Young Master, please go back first.
Don't worry, girls.
Mr. Cheng is busy today.
You always say that.
But Mr. Cheng
really beat you.
Well.
After today, he can't control me anymore.
Father.
You lost.
Roaming the Jianghu,
I keep my word.
You won't cheat, will you?
You won.
Until we meet again.
Retreat!
This bandit is quite reasonable.
It's not easy to cover the face in broad daylight.
Shut up.
Hurry up.
The auspicious hour is coming.
Go.
Why did you withdraw?
After a while,
I'll get the car back.
And we've never returned empty-handed
since we formed the escort team.
That female escort
is even stronger than me.
You all go.
Don't follow me anymore.
My lord, my lord.
Where are you going?
Don't abandon us.
The White Wolves just let Su Yuejiao go.
Why are they coming back?
It seems that the boss means that even if we don't rob,
we can't let others rob.
Boss, is this escort so valuable?
It's my first time encountering this situation.
Uh.
You two go first.
I'll cover your retreat. Meet in Ning'an City.
They're actually trying to fight to the death.
They actually want us to help.
Let's see who dares to lay a finger on her.
Charge!
No speed limit today.
Rush to the auspicious hour.
Chase them!
Who are they?
I've never seen them before.
But they are more desperate than us.
Is there a big treasure on the escort cart?
Chase!
Let my sword taste some blood.
Wait, boss.
Calm down.
That female escort is so powerful.
She can handle
these guys.
Indeed.
But we
didn't get anything today,
and one of us was injured by you.
The point is,
it's time for dinner.
Ladies,
I just came back from Yunjing,
and learned a new song.
I'm not good at it,
so I want to ask you for help.
You're not good at it?
Come on, let's hear it.
♪In a few days,♪
♪I see a lifetime.♪
♪As if unaware of sorrow's taste♪
♪Ask where sorrow originates♪
♪All the winds pass by the ear♪
This stupid invention is killing me.
Brother!
Are you okay?
Is she crazy?
Shall we keep chasing?
Forget it!
We're almost at Ning'an County.
Should we go into the city to rob?
What if the boss blames us?
Take this back.
Just say the other side fled in panic.
We've taught them a lesson.
Yes.
Fortunately,
we can still make it to the auspicious hour.
Go!
Dad,
this fish is just steamed. Have a taste.
I'm not in the mood.
I'm worried about
Jiaojiao's marriage.
Dad.
A bailiff named Zhen
just moved to the east of the city.
He has a son.
Uncle.
Do you think I'm a fool?
There's no bailiff in the east of the city.
Is it just a cat or a dog?
No way!
Who dares to marry into our family
in Yunjing City?
She drove away
all the good men, didn't she?
Fine.
Do you want him or not?
Alas!
In your eyes,
even a god is not good enough for her.
You don't want her to get married at all.
I'm the only one in this family
who really cares about her.
If she doesn't get married,
according to the rules set by my mother,
she won't be able to run this family.
Zhen,
you founded this escort agency,
and Yu'er took it to greater heights.
Later, the old burying the young...
Dad, eat the fish.
Dad.
My world fell apart.
Jiaojiao had to run the agency at a young age.
She could quit,
but I took over.
It's been ten years.
Three years.
By the way, Dad,
Jiaojiao will be back soon.
Why don't we invite him over?
They can meet first.
Hehe.
Ah.
Li Shi, what's wrong?
It's nothing, dad.
Yeah.
Hehe.
It must be Jiaojiao cursing me.
When you come back,
I'll give you a big surprise.
You've only been to Yunjing for a few days.
You miss us so much.
Don't flatter yourself.
He's thinking about
the Nebula Assembly,
not you.
I heard the Grand Tutor held it for the Official.
That means
Mr. Cheng will soon enter officialdom
and rise rapidly in the world.
Ah.
That's just
his wishful thinking.
are just his wishful thinking.
I just
want to enjoy the beauty of Yunjing,
the fine wine and the beautiful women.
Young Master,
if we don't leave now, we won't make it to Yunjing.
Oh, right.
Ladies,
I'm in a hurry to get married.
I'll take my leave now.
See you later.
Getting married?
Congratulations!
Haha, congratulations!
Mr. Cheng, congratulations!
Congratulations!
Dad.
Good.
He knows to come out and greet us.
It seems that marriage works.
I've got the girl I like.
I'll settle down.
I'll live a good life in the future.
I won't let you worry.
Has this brat really changed?
Yicheng.
Master.
When will the escort cart arrive?
It should be here by now.
I'll wait at the door.
I'll go with you to greet her.
Master Cheng, it's your big day.
I've prepared a modest gift
as a token of my respect.
Congratulations, Young Master Cheng.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Please come inside.
Congratulations, Young Master Cheng.
Thank you.
Please come in.
Congratulations.
Yicheng,
are you sure you gave it to that female escort?
Yes.
She personally took the contract.
But four hours have passed.
Why hasn't she shown up yet?
Young Master
Is the bride regretting the marriage?
I'm afraid she'll regret...
I'm afraid she'll regret the marriage.
So
I won't give the rest of the betrothal gifts to her family
until she gets on the escort cart.
It shouldn't happen like this.
My Lord is back.
My Lord
Was there a robber on the way?
and the escort can't beat them?
My Lord,
are you alright?
I'm fine.
What time is it now?
Can we make it to the third auspicious hour
and go straight to the Cheng Mansion?
Miss Yan, hold on tight.
Go!
So,
Su Yuejiao and the escort went to Ning'an County,
and this is all you brought back?
Silk,
cotton,
waterproof,
for tying cargo,
for hanging...
That Su girl is really tough.
Oh, young master,
Su Yuejiao made me look bad in public.
At least break her leg.
If her leg doesn't break,
then break yours.
Young Master
Enough!
You guys, take these scraps
and get out!
You two, take this and get out!
How many times have I said it?
I used to do this because the agency wasn't big.
But times have changed.
Dad, stop lecturing.
You know what Su Yuejiao said about me.
If I don't take revenge,
I won't be a Fu.
You brat.
What do you want to be?
You
don't know
what long-term planning is.
So what if you robbed her?
Dad.
What can you do?
With the relationship between our agency and the Grand Tutor,
If you marry Zhang Xiyun,
the Grand Tutor's daughter,
our business will expand
to the border.
Is it so difficult to take over the Su's Escort Agency?
Dad, I'd love to.
But Zhang Xiyun is a bookworm.
Can I match her?
You are a loser.
You haven't tried,
how do you know you can't match her?
You should get closer first.
Maybe
she'll fall for you.
That's right.
My dad is right.
I'm handsome.
She's pretty.
I'm really into her.
You are a lecher.
You're the same.
This way, please.
Miss Yan, we've arrived at Cheng Mansion.
You can tidy up in the carriage first.
I'll keep watch outside.
Miss Yan, are you feeling unwell?
Where is she?
I don't know.
She just ran into the city.
She was afraid of being late.
She didn't waste a moment.
Oh, no.
Will it fall because we run too fast?
The dart is gone.
What's the use of running fast?
Boss
I'll go back to find it.
Go now.
It's too late.
Why are you here?
Take this.
Boss, you saved my life.
It doesn't matter to be cut.
Share this with my brothers.
What do you mean?
I don't want to be a bandit anymore.
What do you want to do?
We are willing to follow you.
Be an escort.
Young Master Cheng,
I'll find
the people right away.
I'll give you the escort silver back.
But can you
give me more time?
More time?
Look at the decorations,
and the guests
in the hall.
How about this?
I'll go in and tell them
that you lost the bride.
Young Master Cheng, please don't!
Su's Escort Agency never had such a situation.
If anything happens to your wife,
I'm willing to die for it.
Please,
let the escort agency go.
I have an idea.
Everything is ready
here,
only the bride is missing.
Your purpose is pure,
and escorting the bride is the most important thing.
Why don't you
be the bride?
You have a point.
It's not what you think.
It's a stalling tactic.
I'll ask Gong Xi to find a bride.
He's quick; he'll return to take my place.
You can kiss the bride,
and I can finish the escort mission.
Two birds with one stone.
Chief Escort Su
Don't bother.
She'll be fine.
How do you know?
Look at the neat wedding dress.
It's placed on the carriage.
Obviously, she has planned it all along.
She ran away.
She eloped?
Yes.
Let's go.
Rocks in the way.
We're cleaning them up.
We won't be late for your auspicious hour.
Chief Escort Su,
I don't have time to explain now.
After I finish this escort,
I'll give you the escort fee as usual.
No need to report to the authorities,
nor to compensate.
How about killing two birds with one stone?
Chief Escort Su,
I'm begging you.
My future happiness depends on you.
Hmm.